TINEKE NASEEF

USER EXPERIENCE DESIGNER | SHE/HER

Westminster, CO 80031 | telnaseef@gmail.com | 720-203-6631

LinkedIn: https://bit.lv/3fCTHis | Portfolio: https://bit.lv/2ZOMIEb

ABOUT ME

I am a highly adaptable and resourceful designer, combining creative problem solving and analytical skills with an attention to detail to create intuitive, accessible, usable solutions. As a highly-motivated hard-worker, I value organization and am equipped to work well in teams, as well as independently. Having a background in customer service, social media, and communication (as well as expertise in Dutch and German) makes me a highly versatile UX designer and researcher.

EXPERIENCE

pReTravel - https://tnaseef.github.io/UX Portfolio/pretravel.html

An app for researching experiences and vistas at travel destinations

- User Experience and User Interface Designer
- Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Xd, Figma, FlowMapp, Google Drive, InVision, Uxpressia.com

GeekMeet - https://tnaseef.github.io/UX Portfolio/geekmeet.html

A community and interest-sharing app, specifically designed for self-identified "geeks" and "nerds."

- User Experience and User Interface Designer
- Figma, Google Drive, Google Forms, InVision, Miro, Whimsical

Castix LLC

April 2022 - Present

Remote, EU

Principal UX Designer - Volunteer

- Designing and building game's primary site and wiki site
- Assisting game design team on research, ideation, and UI redesign
- Analyzing existing materials, and presenting findings and suggestions
- Rapidly learning multiple technologies to better grasp team's capabilities

Juniper Village - Spearly Center

Front Desk Receptionist

- Managed internal communications
- Ensured positive experience for guests, patients and employees
- Provided research and ideation on experience and efficiency improvements

American DataBank

Nov 2019 - Sep 2020

March 2021 - May 2021

Compliance and Immunization Team Member

- Reviewed approximately 700-800 documents per day
- Exceeded quota on over 90% of shifts
- Provided feedback and ideas to streamline review process
- Wrote copy for standardized document rejection notes

Denver, CO

Denver, CO

American DataBank

Applicant Success Team Member

Jan 2019 - Nov 2019 Denver, CO

- Assisted users and clients through phone, ticket, and email channels
- Interacted with 100-200 users and clients per day
- Found innovative and resourceful solutions to user issues
- Organized project designing an FAQ page
- Processed around 100 background checks and/or document reviews per week
- Wrote copy for standardized responses to emails and chats

Layer3 TV / T-Mobile

July 2018 - Oct 2018

Denver, CO

Concierge Specialist, Social Media

- Assisted users through Twitter and Facebook
- Helped train a team of approximately 20 representatives
- Processed around 50 social media queries per shift
- Tested and monitored streaming services

Layer3 TV / T-Mobile

May 2017 - July 2018

Denver, CO

Layer3 Customer Care Concierge

- Provided exceptional customer service through phone, email and tickets
- Helped 30-50 users and processed around 20 tickets per shift
- Served as primary liaison with engineering team
- Tested and monitored streaming services
- Wrote copy for standardized responses to tickets, emails, and chats

TECHNICAL SKILLS

UX/UI: Ideation, Interactive Design, Prototyping, Public Speaking/Presentation, Responsive Design, User Interviews, User Research, User Testing, Visual Design, Wireframing

DESIGN: Editing, Photo Editing, Photography, Social Media, Songwriting, Voiceover, Web Design, Writing **SOFTWARE**: Adobe Illustrator, Adobe Photoshop, Adobe Xd, Bootstrap, Figma, GitHub, Google Analytics, Google Drive, InVision, Jira, Microsoft Office Suite, Miro, Sketch, Trello

LANGUAGES: CSS, C++, HTML, JavaScript, jQuery

EDUCATION

Certificate in UX/UI, University of Denver Associate of General Studies Degree, Front Range Community College September 2021

May 2021